There is a woman there.
In those days, in your past, you used to wear some beads.
You have done away with these beads. You no longer wear beads but now,
the challenge you are facing now is you have no settled home.
No single man can please you.
No one can give you the kind of affection you want.
This has bastardised your career.
You are just from one place to another. But right now, you are tired.
You don't know what is wrong with you.
Please come out, Jesus loves you.
You are there, you are getting old.
And this will tell on your children. You are there.
You were wearing beads in the past.
Right now, you have stopped using them for a long time.
There is a problem you have. You have no settled home. You move from one place to another.
No one can give you what you want. Please come, come out. Jesus loves you.
You`ve put on a native. Thank you.
Prophecy time.
My name is Sylvia Ogbebor. I'm from Nigeria.
What the Man of God said, that a lady was wearing beads before.
In my school days, I was always putting on those beads.
I got married in 2012. A one year old marriage and we broke up after one year with a child.
The child is with me.
Now, I can`t stay with any man who can satisfy me. I don`t see anything good in any man.
Then I travelled from one country to another, looking for men.
I have been to Dubai like five times and Turkey doing prostitution.
Man of God, please help me.
That is why I called you out.
No one can get you out of this mess. Unless the person sees the need of destroying those beads.
Simple.
It takes the grace of God to see those beads.
If ten men queue, they cannot satisfy you. It's a curse.
So you believed nobody can satisfy you in Nigeria - "let me go to Dubai" .
"Okay let me live my life and let them be enjoying me" - yet you cannot be satisfied;
it's a curse.
So, don't worry. You will give testimony. That is why I called you. It will be over.
Thank You, Jesus!
It is over.
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
That was the message of prophecy from the anointed Man of God.
And the last word was, "it is over".
This prophecy brought about deliverance in the life of this sister.
And she is back here today, to testify to the goodness of God in her life.
The importance of prophecy in the ministry of our Lord Jesus Christ cannot be over-emphasised.
Remember all the words the Man of God said in his prophecy
are things that are very difficult for anyone to come out and talk about, to share with people.
And today, whatever you are going to hear from our sister is not meant to deride her
but to give glory to God Almighty because confession is also part of deliverance.
So right now, she wants to share her experience and also share her testimony to the glory of God.
So let us listen to her.
Sister, once again we welcome you to The SCOAN. Can you please introduce yourself
and let us hear your experience and your testimony.
Emmanuel! (God with us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Ogbebor Sylvia.
This is my mother, Mrs Veronica Ogbebor, and my son.
Last Sunday, I was here with a lot of expectation.
While I was sitting, the Man of God came very close to me and then he left.
My courage was almost gone, but when he came again, he said if you have a grudge,
against anyone, we should forgive them.
Ask the Holy Spirit to come to you, and then you should forgive.
Immediately, I sat down and said this prayer is not for me.
It's too painful, that I can't even forgive him.
Then, he walked down again and said, "I say you should forgive".
Then, I stood up and said, "I have forgiven him" and at that moment he mentioned my case.
He prophesied and said there is a lady who wore beads before
but has done away with them.
He said because of those beads, I could not make a home and they had spoiled my career
and that I could not stay with a man.
He said it will affect my children and that I was getting old.
These are the things that I had been sitting and thinking about alone for the past three weeks,
wondering where this problem is coming from.
When he mentioned it, I came out.
He said that my case would be settled and that I would share my testimony.
Really, what the Man of God said is true.
In those days when I was 22 years old, my neighbour called me
and said that I should follow her somewhere.
On getting to that place, there was a spiritualist who told her that they would perform
some rituals on me, like giving me a mark on my private parts and giving me beads
as an object of seduction on my waist.
All that while, it was uncontrollable.
Then I got an admission. While I was in school, I was moving from one place to another.
I went to Abuja, Port Harcourt and Ghana, doing prostitution.
At the end of the day, during my 300 level, I had an encounter with a ritualist,
which made me say, "I have to quit this before I die".
Then after my graduation in 2010, I went back to my mother's house in Lagos.
That was when I met the man that I had a baby for.
I also had a group of friends that were into prostitution too.
One of them asked me, "Why are you like this? You are no longer pretty, you are looking so unkempt".
I told them that I was not doing prostitution anymore,
that I had changed and was serving God.
They said, "This is not how to serve God. They have brainwashed you".
They said that I should take them to Abuja since I had been there before.
I should show them the way and where they should go.
I told them that I don't have money to do all of that. They then transported me down to Abuja.
We were in a hotel there. I met with an honourable in the National Assembly whom I knew before.
He gave me some money; then we came back to Lagos.
By the time we got to Lagos, they asked me what I wanted to do with the money.
I told them that I wanted to rent a house where I could stay with my mom and rent a shop for business.
They said that I should rather travel to Turkey as they had already applied for their visas.
I agreed with them and applied for my Turkish visa.
Then, I met with my baby's farther and got pregnant for him.
Throughout the one year period that I was married to him, it was hell.
He beat me up so much, even when I was nine months pregnant.
The doctors examined me and confirmed I would deliver on a Sunday.
It was on a Friday when they confirmed the Sunday delivery.
It was on that same Friday when he beat me up.
My child almost died in the womb; I had to be rushed to the hospital
where a caesarean section was carried out on me.
After three months, he threw me out of the house.
I was serving as a National Youth Service Corps member
and my mom was in the same house with us.
He threw me and our child out, so I went back to my mom.
I was there; after the service, I went back to Abuja.
Upon getting to Abuja, I met a girl from the same group of girls who were doing prostitution.
I didn't get the job that I was going there for; she then suggested that we travel to Dubai.
I said "No", as I had not travelled before and I didn't have money for a visa.
She said that she would provide the visa for me and that I should just get a flight ticket.
That was when I started the prostitution again.
I looked for money for a ticket to go to Dubai and eventually the visa was out.
I couldn't get the money for the ticket to Dubai. She then said that she would pay for everything.
and once I got to Dubai, I would pay her back.
I agreed and we went to Dubai.
She said that when we get to Dubai, there would be a queue and within two weeks
I would be able to make the money to pay her back.
Then, I'd start making my own money to rent a house to stay in, with my mom and child.
What is the queue all about?
The queue of men that would be coming into the house where the ladies are staying.
Upon getting to Dubai,
I used to see Dubai on the TV. Dubai is a very beautiful place.
But the particular place she took me to was a market area;
African people dominated that place.
I asked her how I was going to start getting money so that I could pay her back immediately.
She said that that was where I was going to work.
She took me to a room with four beds; they were divided by curtains.
Men would come in there.
I told her that I could not do it. Then, she took my passport.
They said that I could not leave the country without a passport.
I had to start doing what she asked me to do, despite the fact that I had stiches
because after the operation, the wound re-opened; I was still going for treatment to dress the wound.
Like the Man of God said, even if 10 men queued, I would not get tired, which was true.
The men were always trooping in.
So how many men would come to you in a day?
Between 30 to 40 a day.
At that point in time, you were still nursing the wound of the operation?
Yes, I still had the wound which had not yet healed.
I came back to Nigeria and met my mom with my child in the same condition. They were looking so unkempt.
I said, "This will not continue" so I went to Abuja and Port Harcourt again to raise some money.
Then I went back to the same place.
When you went to Abuja and Port Harcourt, how did you raise money?
Through prostitution.
Then I raised money and went back to the same place in Dubai.
That was how I was able to raise money, I came back and rented a house to put my mom and child there.
All the time, I was going to and fro Lagos and Dubai.
I eventually came back in March from Dubai because the last time I went to Dubai,
whenever I saw a group of people, I could count 5-6 of them who had used and paid me.
So, all the time I was very shy and scared.
Then, I moved to the hotel where I used social networks.
I would always ask my mom to look after my child as I was going to do business.
Ok, you always told your mom that you were doing business?
Yes.
So you mean your mother was not even aware that you were into prostitution?
By the time I came back, I was sick. I had depression and too many dreams
that made me feel like I couldn't even close my eyes; if I closed my eyes, I would die.
At night, I didn't sleep and during the day time, I was always indoors.
Whenever I was indoors, I would always be busy on my phone, using socal networks to look for men.
When I came back, my son was really sick. I had to rush him to hospital.
I was asking myself how was I going to continue with this, it was too much for me.
I was depressed, I was not sleeping and that urge of sex was always there.
I wanted to sleep with men.
With the group of friends that I had, whenever I didn't see a man,
we would practice lesbianism, smoke marijuana, cigarettes and all that.
The whole thing became just too much for me
I asked myself, "My child is growing, how will I be able to continue with this?"
I told a friend what I was going through. That I couldn't sleep and so,
I asked her to prescribe drugs for me. There was a drug I used to take that always calmed my nerves.
I told her that it wasn't working. I asked her to prescribe another drug. She told me all that I needed was sex.
That was the same lesbian friend who said what I needed was sex.
That I should meet with a man to sleep with me and that would take away the anxiety.
Most of the men who gave me money, I didn't enjoy it with them.
The ones I smoked marijuana and lodged in a hotel with and at the end of the day,
I would give them money, those were the ones that I called.
This time, I needed help. So, I told my mom what I was going through. That I couldn't sleep.
My mom confided in someone who told her that there is a place where she should take me to.
We went there and the woman said that she would bathe me in the river,
I bought a lot of things and sew a white garment and we would go to the river.
The woman said I should bring N80,000 but I did not have that amount.
We then agreed on N20,000 on Friday.
On Saturday, a brother called me and said I should try and go to church on that Sunday.
I agreed and on that Sunday I came to church.
When I came on that Sunday, the Man of God gave the prophecy.
I was scared to come out but then, I thought that that was what was happening to me.
I quickly ran out.
I needed help so I cried out, "Man of God, please help me! I am depressed".
He said that I was free and I would share my testimony.
After my deliverance, I noticed that the whole trouble that was on me like a load,
I had been relieved of it.
When I got home, I decided to confirm my deliverance, by seeing if I could sleep.
When I lied on my bed, I started meditating with my Faith Bracelet.
I noticed that all of the messages the Man of God preached about, were coming back to me,
including the one the evangelist preached titled, 'No Shortcut'.
I kept thinking that all the times I had been moving around were simply shortcuts
and there are so many sins that go with shortcuts.
So that is not the right way to go.
Then I brought out my credentials, thinking they might be useful.
Then, I noticed that whenever I was meditating with my Faith Bracelet, I could sleep.
I could just sleep off only to find out later that I was still holding the bracelet in my hand.
Then I would wear it on my wrist again.
The bad dreams that I used to have are gone.
I used to have an urge for sex and could not resist it any time it came.
So, I tried to lie on my bed to see if that urge would come but it was not coming.
Rather, the messages I had heard and the books I had read were the things that I was meditating on.
So, I believe that I have been delivered. Since then I have been sleeping well.
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
In the course of your testimony, you said that you are a university graduate, right?
Yes.
And because of this spirit and the urge that had been tormenting you,
you forgot all about your credentials and your career.
So it was after your deliverance that you remembered your credentials?
Yes. The Man of God said it was killing my career.
Before now, if you asked me what I wanted to do or become, I would have nothing to say.
Sometimes I was scared, wondering if that was how the world was.
But later, the things which I had studied, started coming back; ideas were coming.
I carried my credentials and thought, "Wow! This is actually for me".
A lot of people I meet out there don't even have this.
"So, why would I have this and still be doing that?"
So, I felt happy within myself.
So now that you're delivered, tell us -
do you still communicate with those friends that you did this job of prostitution with?
That Tuesday, when I got home, for two days, I had kept my phone switched off.
By the time I switched it back on, messages and calls were coming in asking me where I was.
Previously, I would sit down and say, "Don't worry, we will have food; God will do wonders and miracles".
And the miracle I was expecting was for a call to come in and I would quickly go,
and make money and come back.
These calls and messages came in, asking what had happened, as they hadn't heard from me.
I deleted and blocked others - the ones I used to send nude pictures to.
These were the things I was always scared of losing before.
But I was able to delete those things from my phone.
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So tell us once again, since you have been delivered last week till now,
the depression, the urge to smoke or drink - do you still have them?
No, I don't have them.
The urge to smoke was always constant before.
Whenever I would think about things like my baby's father.
The Man of God said I should forgive.
Whenever I thought of those things that put me in the condition I was in,
I wanted to smoke.
So, I would put on my dress and go to any place where I knew it was convenient for me to smoke.
But since then, I have not been smoking and that urge is no longer there.
I have noticed that I am now frequently at home. My child is around me; my children are happy.
With this mood I am in, I am very happy.
Once again, let us put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Thank you very much. We will get back to you. In the meantime, let us listen to your mother.
We believe she also has some experiences to share.
Mama, you're welcome, in Jesus' name.
Can you please tell us your name and share with us the testimony of your daughter's deliverance.
My name is Veronica Ogbe.
And the lady beside you?
She's my last born daughter.
Kindly go ahead.
On Sunday, a call came in; she told me she wanted to go to church.
At around 5 am, she woke up, did her chores and bathed.
I asked her where she wanted to go to; she replied to church. I asked her which church.
She said The SCOAN.
I asked her who will be taking her there. She said one of her friends.
I thanked God that my child was going to church on that day.
She then went to church. We went to our own church.
When we came back, she had not returned yet.
So I decided to call her to find out if it was really church she went to or elsewhere.
When I called her, she told me that she was still in church. I thanked God.
Since God delivered her on Sunday, she has changed!
Please tell us about those changes.
She has changed because before, she would not help with anything in the house.
She would spend a lot of time on her phone.
I would ask her if she wasn't going to put her phone down and get a job so that we could eat.
Later, she would go to bed.
When she woke up, she would shower and then go out in the evening.
Since Sunday, she has been to the market, she has cleaned the house and worked.
This baby, she bathes him and washes his clothes and mine also.
She will go to the market, buy food then come home and cook. We will eat.
So she never used to do all of those things before?
Not at all.
So when she used to go out and travel to Dubai, where did she say she was going to?
Previously, she told me she was going for business. She never told me what she was really into.
That Sunday when the Man of God delivered her, I said, "God, I thank You! Man of God, I thank you!"
Prophecy Testimony
You have heard from the mother, testifying to the deliverance of the daughter.
She said she is so happy that God Almighty finally delivered her daughter.
She never knew that the daughter was into these acts of prostitution for so many years.
That each time the daughter was travelling out of the country or going out,
she would ask her where she was going and she would say that she was going for business.
According to her, she was 24/7 browsing on her phone
and she wouldn't know what she was exactly looking for,
not knowing that she was always getting contacts with men on the phone.
But ever since her daughter has been delivered, she said her attitude has changed.
Before now, she would not sweep or wash anything.
She would not even take care of the baby or even take care of the home.
But now she has started doing all of those things. Her countenance has changed.
She is now happy. She doesn't go out anymore.
She stays indoors except when she is coming to church.
And she said "To God be the glory!"
Once again let us put our hands together for Jesus!
First, I have something to say about Jesus who delivered me.
Jesus is faithful and always ready to accept you, no matter the kind of sins you have committed.
He is always there to tell you, "I love you".
To everyone listening to my testimony out there, I will tell them that if you are believing God
for one thing or another, you should always have faith.
believing that some day, God will answer your prayer.
And to other people I had met out there.
There are a lot of ladies I have met out there; some have two children, others have three
and they always have one excuse or the other for what lured them into doing what they are doing.
I want to tell you that that way is a shortcut and there is always sin that goes along with that way.
Since you are graduating from one level to another, because that was how I was graduating,
I want to tell you that the way which is very easy, step-by-step,
is where you find meekness, happiness and peace of mind.
I want to tell you that Jesus loves you; come back home.
Come back home. Shall we put our hands together for Jesus!
Yes, come back home. Because the Bible says homelessness is man's condition without Christ.
And homelessness is a life that is devoid of Christ.
When Christ is not in our lives, we are homeless.
So come back home, those who are still in the wilderness of prostitution,
and all other crimes and vices that do not please God.
To God be the glory. Now that God Almighty has set you free, we also want to encourage you
to follow the way that you have discovered, the new life that you have found
and the love of Jesus that He has shown you.
Walk in the way of Christ by making His word the standard for your life.
We pray that God Almighty will give you the inner grace to make His word the standard for your life
and the deliverance you have received will be permanent, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Once again let us clap for Jesus Christ!